hbcuconnect.com 2006-12-30

# HBCUCONNECT.COM Terms of Service

HBCUCONNECT.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We only use your personal information to help us to improve our services to you, to provide you with products you have requested, to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you, and to provide you with a member newsletter. 

**How is your information stored and protected?**  
We protect your account information by placing it on the secure portion of our Web site. That's why you have to enter a unique Member Name (email address) and Password each time you want to access your HBCUCONNECT.com account. Your Password should never be shared with anyone. 

**_Please be assured that HBCUCONNECT.com will not view or gather any information regarding the contents of your personal files stored in your HBCUCONNECT.com account unless authorized by you the user.  
_**The personal files that you store in your HBCUCONNECT.com account and other information you provide when you register for the HBCUCONNECT.com service are maintained in a secure environment that is inaccessible to the public. 

**What information does HBCUCONNECT.com collect about you and how is it used?**  
HBCUCONNECT.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our Web site. Some personal information is gathered when you visit HBCUCONNECT.com, including your Internet address and the site from which you visited. If you choose to become an HBCUCONNECT.com member, during registration HBCUCONNECT.com asks for your name, e-mail address, phone number, school name, claim to fame, most memorable moment, current whereabouts. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to HBCUCONNECT.com and are able to take full advantage of HBCUCONNECT.com's many features.

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by HBCUCONNECT.com and/or our partners; and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact HBCUCONNECT.com we may keep a record of that correspondence. HBCUCONNECT.com also asks members to complete surveys.

We use all of the personal information that we collect for research purposes to improve the HBCUCONNECT.com service. In addition, we summarize information about our member’s that is provided to advertisers and partners. Our partners and advertisers use this summary information to provide more relevant information and offers to our members who choose to receive such offers and information. From time to time, we make our member e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. We do not sell data about our users or provide any personally identifiable information about any individual member without their consent. Wherever HBCUCONNECT.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

**Your Opt out choices  
**If, at any time, you wish to stop receiving information from HBCUCONNECT.com, or to have your name and other personal information removed from our list, please let us know by sending us an e-mail request using our  online contact form or writing to us at 750-Q Cross Pointe Rd., Columbus, Ohio 43230. 

**Links to other Web sites  
**Links from our Web site are provided for your convenience only. You should always investigate the privacy practices of all Web sites that you access, including those linking to or from our Web site. HBCUCONNECT.com does not endorse and is not responsible for the content of any third party Web site or the privacy practices of third parties. 

**Legal Compliance  
** HBCUCONNECT.com reserves the right to disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to:

  1. comply with legal process
  2. respond to any claims against it
  3. Protect the rights, property or personal safety of HBCUCONNECT.com, our customers or the public. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
HBCUCONNECT.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, but we will not do so without posting the modified Privacy Policy on our Web site. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you visit our Web site or use the HBCUCONNECT.com service to make sure that you understand how your information will be used. 

**How to reach us regarding privacy questions or concerns**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how your demographic and profile information is used, please contact us at: 

HBCUCONNECT.com   
HBCU Privacy Inquiry  
750-Q Cross Pointe Rd. Columbus, Ohio 43230  

Email: THE STAFF
